itead.cc 2019-09-12

# Privacy Notice

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ITead Studio collects, uses, stores, archives and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of this Web site. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

### The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the iStore website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive services. We may ask for personal information such as Name, Company Name, Address, Phone Number, Email Address and or Credit Card information.

### The Way We Use This Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. We will use information stored in our database about you to provide support. Email addresses and other data collected in support requests are not shared with outside parties unless you have consented as such to provide you with support. We may email directly to our customer lists special promotional offers from outside vendors, partners or suppliers.

ITead Studio uses aggregated, anonymous data for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and iStore’s marketing, advertising and sales efforts. ITead Studio does not use such anonymous information for any other purpose.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

### Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18.

### How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. We may disclose aggregated, anonymous data to investors and potential partners.

### How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call send an email to [**  info@iteadstudio.com**](mailto:info@iteadstudio.com).
